<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">The Thirsty Crow</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="button_start">Start</string>
    <string name="button_return">Return</string>
    <string name="button_about">About</string>
    <string name="toggle_background_audio">Toggle Background Audio</string>
    <string name="button_play">Play</string>
    <string name="button_stop">Stop</string>
    <string name="story_placeholder">A Thirsty Crow..</string>
    <string name="story_part1">One hot day, there was a thirsty crow, looking for water everywhere. 
        For long time, he couldn\'t find any and felt very weak.</string>
    <string name="story_part2">He decided to rest on a tree.
        Suddenly, he saw a pot at some distance.</string>
    <string name="story_part3">He flew towards the pot to drink water.</string>
    <string name="story_part4">Yes, he could see some water inside the pot!
        The crow tried to reach the water, but sadly, he found that the water level was too low.
        Then he tried to push the pot to tilt for the water to flow out but the pot was too heavy.</string>
    <string name="story_part5">The crow thought hard for a while. Then looking around,he saw some pebbles. 
        He suddenly had a good idea. He started picking up the pebbles one by one, dropping each into the pot.
        \n(Hint: Touch the picture to help the crow drop pebbles.)</string>
    <string name="story_part6">As more and more pebbles filled the pot, the water level kept rising. 
                    Soon it was high enough for the crow to drink. </string>
    <string name="story_part7">The crow drank the water and flew away happily.
     \n\n<b>Moral of the story: Where there is a will, there is a way!!!</b></string>
    <string name="about_page">This interactive story telling application narrates one of the best moral stories. 
        \n\nThis beautifully illustrated story uses animated scenes, on click animations and audios to capture the interest of the reading audience.
        \n\nThe application gives the option to read the story yourself or hit the \'Play\' button to let the app read it for you. This great story inspires 
        children and adults to learn respect, good values, ethics, morals and good behavior.
        \n\n© Samiksha Sharma</string>

</resources>